(RUMBLING ROAR)
Doctor, come on, will you? Look!
博士, 快点, 好吗? 快看!
Oh, my word! Into the Tardis. Quickly.
哦, 天哪！进 TARDIS 里去, 快点
Oh, no! If I can't pull this down, we'll get stuck.
噢, 不！如果我没法把这个拉下来,我们就被困住了
That stupid, idiotic...
这个愚蠢傻蛋的...
Doctor, the lava's up to the Tardis!
博士, 熔岩都快到 TARDIS 了!
If I can unstick this stupid, idiotic...
如果我能扯开这个愚蠢傻蛋的...
There we are.
这下好了
- Have you done it?
- It's stopped the fluid links from vaporising.
- 你搞定了？  - 流体连接器不能再蒸发了
- We shan't suffocate.
- If we don't hurry, we'll be fried by the lava.
- 我们不会窒息了  - 如果我们不快但, 我们会被熔岩烧成灰了
- Isn't there any way we can get away?
- Well, there IS an emergency unit, but...
- 我们有什么可能逃脱吗？  - 唔, 是有一个紧急设备, 但是...
- I can't possibly use that.
- But this IS an emergency!
- 我不可能启用那个  - 但是这就是紧急情况啊
But it moves the Tardis out of the
time-space dimension, out of reality!
但它会把 TARDIS 移出时空维度, 推到现实之外去！
Fine. Reality's getting too hot, anyway!
很好．反正现实已经太热了！
I can't possibly use this.
We don't know what will happen.
我不可能启用这个, 我们不知道可能发生什么！
Stop your jabbering and get on with it. Look!
别叨叨了, 赶紧动手吧．看！
(PULSATING WHINE)
Who are you?
你是谁？
(HUMMING INTENSIFIES)
Who are you?
你是谁？
Where are you?
你们在哪儿？
What do you want with me?
你想要我怎么样？
No...
不...
No, I must fight.
不, 我必须抗争
I must fight!
我必须抗争
I will fight!
我会抗争！
The Mind Robber
(Whopix fan edit)
思维强盗
(Whopix 粉丝剪辑版)